<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gabriele Orazi</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Gabriele Orazi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Gabriele Orazi</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:53:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thoughts after my first DEF CON</title><link>/posts/defcon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:53:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/defcon/</guid><description>My first @DEFCON 31 is just gone. I heavily wondered about how it would have been and, honestly, it just crashed my expectations. I came home with a thousand ideas and a great desire to get to work to improve. Basically, I&amp;rsquo;m now fully charged for the upcoming academic year!
Here some of my newbie&amp;rsquo;s random thoughts/tips: 👇
Stickers, stickers everywhere! I was planning to leave my laptop free from stickers, but now it will be so hard to stick (lol) to the plan.</description></item><item><title>Activities &amp; Services</title><link>/activities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 17:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/activities/</guid><description>Talks &amp;ldquo;Digital documents pitfalls: Security and Privacy&amp;rdquo; - November 3rd 2022, UniPd course Advanced Topics in Computer and Network Security &amp;ldquo;RedactBuster: Robustness Analysis of Document Redaction for Personally Identifiable Information Protection&amp;rdquo; - February 16th 2024, TUDelft &amp;ldquo;Acoustic Side-Channel Attacks on a Computer Mouse&amp;rdquo; - July 18th 2024, DIMVA 2024 (EPFL) &amp;ldquo;RedactBuster: Entity Type Recognition from Redacted Documents&amp;rdquo; - September 18th 2024, ESORICS 2024 (Politechnika Bydgoska) Services Web Chair 1st Workshop on DevSecOps Research and Opportunities (DevSecOpsRO), co-located with EuroS&amp;amp;P 2023 2nd Workshop on DevSecOps Research and Opportunities (DevSecOpsRO), co-located with EuroS&amp;amp;P 2024 3rd Workshop on DevSecOps Research and Opportunities (DevSecOpsRO), co-located with EuroS&amp;amp;P 2025 Technical Program Committee Member Workshop on AI for Cyber Threat Intelligence (WAITI) 2024, co-located with the ACSAC 2024</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>/publications/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 17:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/publications/</guid><description>Publications My research areas are focused on privacy and private data leaks. I&amp;rsquo;m primarely working on obfuscation techniques, forensics and malware detection.
RedactBuster: Entity Type Recognition from Redacted Documents Context analysis on sentences with redacted information can enable entity recognition. @ ESORICS 2024 M. Beltrame, M. Conti, P. Guglielmin, F. Marchiori, G. Orazi Acoustic Side-Channel Attacks on a Computer Mouse An innovative information leakage attack based on mice noise. @ DIMVA 2024 M.</description></item><item><title>Short Bio</title><link>/shortbio/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 17:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/shortbio/</guid><description>Short Bio English Gabriele Orazi holds a Ph.D. in Brain, Mind and Computer Science (BMCS), with a focus on privacy, obfuscation, cyber forensics, and malware detection. He conducts research at the University of Padua as part of the SPRITZ Security and Privacy Research Group, under the supervision of Prof. Mauro Conti. As part of his Ph.D., he spent six months as a visiting researcher at UCI.
Before his doctoral studies, he earned a double Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science (Cyber Security) from the University of Trento and the University of Turku.</description></item><item><title>Suggestions</title><link>/suggestions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 17:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/suggestions/</guid><description>📚 Books Some of the books that I read and that I can definitively recommend.
Atomic Habits - James Clear [EN] [IT] The Subtle Art of Not Giving A F*ck - Mark Manson [EN] [IT] Scrum: The Art of Doing Twice the Work in Half the Time - Jeff Sutherland [EN] [IT] Getting Things Done: The Art of Stress-free Productivity - David Allen [EN] Permanent Record - Edward Snowden [EN] [IT] Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance - Robert M.</description></item><item><title>Teaching activities</title><link>/teaching/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 17:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/teaching/</guid><description>Teaching activities Along my journey in academia, I had the chance to be a teaching assistant of professors from University of Padua, as well as few other experiences as lecturer.
A.A. 2025/2026 [BSc] FISICA, MATEMATICA, STATISTICA E INFORMATICA, Professor for undergraduate program of Scienze e tecnologie erboristiche at Unipd DSF [BSc] STATISTICA E BIOLOGIA QUANTITATIVA 1, Professor for undergraduate program of Biologia at DiBio Unipd A.A. 2023/2024 [MSc] CyberSecurity and Cryptography: Principles and Practices - teaching assistant with prof.</description></item><item><title>How to create free static website with Hugo and Github Pages</title><link>/posts/github_pages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/github_pages/</guid><description>So you&amp;rsquo;re struggling to create your own website? Are you looking for some cheap and clean solution too? Free?
Ok, probably you&amp;rsquo;re a bit too ambitious.
OR NOT.
I was in your situation too and now you&amp;rsquo;re visiting this website, which is built on top of the same advices you&amp;rsquo;re going to follow (hopefully!).
If you unfortunately fall into this website, probably you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with the git versioning system. Probably you know about Github as well.</description></item><item><title>whoami</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 17:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>whoami Adaptable, hyperactive and tireless, I like challenges and adventures. I always wonder why things happen. I have difficulties in surviving without running, cycling and climbing. I do research in the InfoSec field. Currently based in Padua, working with SPRITZ research group.
Education I fell in love with Bologna, where I studied Computer Science for my Bachelor. Did you ever seen a bot for a smartphone game? That’s what I did with RoboRK for my Bachelor thesis!</description></item></channel></rss>